なぜだ？ どうなっている？
オカリン 待ってよ～
どうしちゃったの？
アキバから ｢萌え｣が
すべて 消失しまったというのか？
Why?
｢とらのあな｣も ｢アニメイト｣も
どこに いったのだ？
What's going on?
｢まんだらけ｣や ｢ゲーマーズ｣は？
All the moe is gone from Akiba?
何 言ってるの？ オカリン
Okarin, wait up!
そんなの アキバにあるわけないよ
Okarin!
だから
まゆしぃは 中野まで 同人誌を…
What's wrong?
Where's the Tora no Ana? The Animate?
まゆり お前 メイクイーンで
バイトしていたよな？
The Mandarake? The Gamers?
メイクイーンって？
What are you talking about, Okarin?
Why would those be in Akiba?
｢メイクイーン＋ニャン２｣だ！
That's why I'm going to Nakano to get my doujinshi.
バカな…
Mayuri,
you work part-time at May Queen, right?
アキバに 萌え文化を
取り入れるように お願いしたのは
May Queen?
フェイリスなのニャン
May Queen Nyan Nyan!
それを否定するＤメールを
過去に 送ったのか？
Impossible...
たった１通のメールで 町が
まるまる 改変されるなんて…
Feyris was the one who asked
to bring moe culture to Akiba.
She sent a D-mail, preventing that from ever happening?
With just one message,
the whole town changed.
Chaos Theory Homeostasis
あっ…
メイクイーンがあった場所とは
とても 思えん
It's hard to believe that
May Queen used to be here.
メークインって じゃがいも？
May Queen? That a potato?
夏は
じゃがバタより つけ麺っしょ
During summer, I prefer noodles to potatoes.
だから じゃがいもの話ではなく…
It isn't a potato...
メイクイーンがなければ
If May Queen never existed,
then how did we meet Feyris?
俺たちは フェイリスと
どうやって 知り合ったんだ？
まっ 確かに
フェイリスたんと 知り合えたのは
Well, it's thanks to potato ramen that we met her.
じゃがバタラーメンの
おかげだけど
どういうことだ？
What do you mean?
忘れたん？
池袋で 雷ネットの大会があった日
You've forgotten?
The day of the Rai-Net Tournament in Ikebukuro,
お昼に食べた じゃがバタラーメン
のせいで おなか壊して
I got sick from the potato ramen I had for lunch,
僕がリタイアして…
それで？
so I withdrew.
代わりに
オカリンとまゆ氏が 参戦して
And then?
Mayushii and you entered as a pair,
その時の対戦相手が
フェイリスたん
and you went up against Feyris-tan.
オカリンたちは 惨敗したんだけど
You totally lost,
その時から
まゆ氏とフェイリスたんは
but Mayushii and Feyris-tan became friends.
お友達になったんしょ
なるほど…
I see.
見て 見て るかちゃん
Look, look, Ruka-chan.
昨日 中野で買った
レイヤーさん写真集
I bought this cosplayer
photo book yesterday, in Nakano!
過去は変わっても
So cute...
The past changed, but our relationships haven't?
結果的に 現在の人間関係は
変わってないということか…
盆休みだというのに 随分
暇そうだな ラボメンガールズよ
You seem to have lots of time
on your hands, this Obon, Lab Member Girls.
お邪魔してます
ほら かわいいでしょ
Hello, there.
Look! Cute, huh?
おお～ ブラチューのセドナコス
Hey! It's Sedona from Blood Tune!
作り込み すごいでしょ？
水着もあるよ
It's really detailed!
There's a swimsuit version, too.
憧れるな 僕 こんなに
スタイル 良くないから…
I wish I could be like that.
I don't have those proportions.
大丈夫 貧乳は正義なんだよ
It's okay!
Flat is justice!
そうだ 今度 ラボメンのみんなで
海に行こうよ！
I know!
Why not take all the lab members,
and go to the beach?
紅莉栖ちゃんも 一緒に！
With Kurisu-chan!
全員 スク水で おｋ？
Everyone wears their school swimsuits, okay?
HENTAIと海水浴なんて…
I'm not going swimming with a pervert.
ええ～
ああ～ つまり その
女子メンバー限定ってことなら
Um, well... I mean, if it's just the girls,
喜んで参加させてもらう
ってことで
I'd love to!
ハハハッ 素直になったらどうだ？
クリスティーナ
Why not be honest, Christina?
｢私は でん部の蒙古斑を
見られたくないので
You don't want
anyone to see the mole on your rear,
一緒には行けません｣と
so you can't go.
なっ… 蒙古斑なんてないわよ！
There's no mole!
それに
そもそも 女子メンバー限定ならば
And if it's just the girls,
そこのルカ子も無理ではないか
はっ？ なんでよ？
then Rukako can't go.
Huh? Why not?
いやっ この前 教えただろ？
ルカ子は 正真正銘の男だと
I told you earlier, right?
That Rukako's actually a guy.
えっ？
あっ…
ぬっ…
ええ？
最悪ね あんた…
You know, you're a jerk.
女の子に向かって
男呼ばわりなんて
How can you call a girl a guy?
Mayushii doesn't like it
when you say stuff like that.
そういうこと言うの
まゆしぃ 好きじゃないな
さすがに マズくね？
Isn't that really mean?
はああ…
ちょ ちょ… ちょっと待て
なぜ 泣いている？
Wait!
Why are you crying?
謝りなさい 今すぐ 漆原さんに
Apologize to Urushibara-san. Now.
謝るも何も 俺は真実しか…
No, seriously.
Why would I apologize? It's true—
いいんです！
It's fine!
僕 岡部さんに そういうふうに
見られていたんですね…
So that's what you think of me, Okabe-san.
いや いや いや ルカ子 お前は…
いつまで 続ける気？
No, no, no, Rukako! You're really...
How long will you keep that up?
僕 帰ります
I'm going home!
待て！ 俺を担ぐのは よせ！
Wait!
You're a guy!
お前は正真正銘の男だ！
Look! Right here, you have...
なぜなら ここに…
ああっ？
ああっ！
あれっ？ ない… ないぞ！
It's gone! There's nothing here!
岡部さん やめてくだ…
Okabe-san, stop it...
ルカ子
Rukako, you're a girl?
お前… 女なのか？
最初から そう言っとるだろうが！
I've been saying that this whole time!
おっ？
お～っす！ あっ… どうかした？
Hey... What's wrong?
気にするな 軽く拷問を…
Don't worry about it.
拷問？ まさか 牧瀬 紅莉栖に？
Just a bit of torture...
Torture?
By Makise Kurisu?
ああ…
だが 誤解は解けた… はずだ
Yes, but I fixed the misunderstanding.
I think...
足を攻められたの？
She got your legs?
どうあ～！
今 足に 触れてはならん！
Don't touch my legs!
小一時間 正座をさせられ…
She made me sit on my knees for an hour!
いや… 拷問を受けたあとなのだ
No! I mean, I was tortured.
なんだ
そんなの 拷問のうちに入らないよ
Oh... That isn't torture.
まるで 本当の拷問を
受けたかのような口ぶりだな
You almost sound like you've been tortured.
そりゃ 戦士だからね
Well, I am a soldier.
絶好の サイクリング日和だね
It's a perfect day for cycling...
そうか？
Yeah?
あのさあ…
ちょっと サイクリングしない？
Hey...
Want to go for a ride?
うん？
はあ… はあ…
これを…
サイクリングと… 言うのか？
Is this what you call cycling?
あたしさ 東京に来たのは
I came to Tokyo to find my dad.
父さんを
捜索するためだったんだよね
To find him?
捜索？ 蒸発でもしたのか？
Did he disappear or something?
もう 何年も会ってなくて
顔も覚えていないんだ
I haven't seen him in years.
I can't even remember his face.
この町にいることは
分かってるんだけどね
But I know he's in this city.
手がかりは これだけ
This is my only clue...
父さんが持ってたピンバッジ
A badge he used to own.
Then you shouldn't just kill time at
a part-time job, should you?
ならば のん気に バイトなど
している場合ではないだろう
いろいろ事情があってね
There's some stuff going on, you know?
でも
一度だけ チャンスはあるんだ
But there's one chance.
えっ？
My dad might show up tomorrow,
at a certain place.
明日 ある場所に
父さんが 現れるかもしれない
それを逃したら
If I miss that, I'll have to leave this town.
あたしは この町を
離れなきゃいけないんだけどね
行かなきゃいけないところが
あるの
There's somewhere I have to go.
あたしも 多忙な訳よ
I'm busy, you know?
まあ もともと 会えなかったら
Well, I was always planning on
giving up if I couldn't meet him.
諦めるつもりだったんだけどさ
フフン… 不安なのだな？
分かるぞ その気持ち
You're uneasy, aren't you?
I can understand that feeling.
だが しかし！
But too bad, part-time soldier!
残念だったな バイト戦士よ
Your luck ran out, the minute
you spoke to the great
Mad Scientist, Hououin Kyouma.
マッドサイエンティストである
この俺に相談したのが 運のツキ
お前は 今日から
ラボメンNo.008だ！
You are now Lab Member 008!
俺たちの実験台となってもらう
You will be our guinea pig.
どっ どうするの？
Wh-What are you going to do?
Change the past.
過去を変えるのだ
非道と思うなら 思え
You may think me cruel if you like.
だが もはや 逃れられぬ
But there is no escape for you.
お前は 蒸発する前の父親に
Ｄメールを送るのだ
Send a D-mail to your father, before he leaves.
｢娘を置いていくな｣とな
Tell him not to leave his daughter behind.
フ～ッ アッハハハハ…
君って いいヤツだね
You're a good person, you know that?
なにっ!?
なんか…
What?
I feel a bit better now, somehow.
ちょっとだけ 楽になったかも
そろそろ 戻らなくちゃ
I have to get back.
心配してくれて サンキュ
Thanks for talking to me!
いいか！ 明日
Listen!
Whether you see him tomorrow or not,
父親に 会えても 会えなくても
必ず ラボに来い！
come by the lab!
お前の傷心を利用し
Ｄメール実験をしてやる
I will use your sentimentality
for an experiment with the D-mail!
アッハハハハ…
さすが マッドサイエンティスト！
You really are a mad scientist!
That's terrible...
悪逆非道だね
アッハハハハ… ウフフ
ウフフフフ…
では これより 作戦名
I will now explain
the parameters of Operation Eldhrímnir.
｢エルドフリームニル｣の
概要について 説明する
また 北欧神話？
More Norse myths?
If the part-time warrior meets her father,
バイト戦士が 父親に会えたなら
祝いの会
we'll hold a celebration...
東京での最後の晩さんを 執り行う
A last supper in Tokyo, for her.
そして
もし会えなかったときは 残念会
And if she doesn't,
we will try to cheer her up,
その後 Ｄメールの実験だ
and then send a D-mail.
あれ？ ダル君がいないよ
Where's Daru?
｢今夜は オフ会があるから
参加できない｣などと
He's meeting his online friends tonight,
so he said he can't join us.
ふざけたことを言ってきた
The fool!
だが 既に 手は打ってある
But I've taken steps.
このメールを 先ほど送っておいた
To: Daru
Subject: Now is the time to choose
Feyris's cooking or your meeting.
Which will you choose?
I sent this message.
｢フェイリスの手料理とオフ会
Feyris's cooking or your meeting.
どっちを選ぶのだ？｣
Which will you choose?
ええ～ だって フェリスちゃんは
来られないんでしょ？
But Feyris-chan can't come, right?
フェイリスは バイト戦士と
面識はないので しかたないが
Feyris has never met the part-time warrior,
so it can't be helped.
ダルは
この作戦に参加する義務がある
But Daru has a duty to
participate in this operation.
あの… 僕も
Um... I've never met this Suzuha-san...
その 鈴羽さんっていう人には
会ったことないんですけど…
かまわん お前たちには
宴会用の買い出しに 行ってもらう
That's fine.
I'm sending you all shopping for the banquet.
あんたは？
And you?
I will follow the part-time warrior
バイト戦士を尾行し
状況を 逐一 報告する
and report in on the situation.
やめなさい 親子水入らずに
させてやりなさいよ
Don't you dare.
Let the father and daughter
have their time together.
そうだよ オカリンも
一緒に 買い出しに行こう
That's right.
Come shopping with us!
I'm following her—
俺は尾行を…
だから ダメだっつってんでしょ！
I said no!
Don't tell me what to do, assistant...
助手の分際で 俺に指図するな…
また 正座する？
今度は３時間ほど…
You want to sit on your knees again?
This time, for three hours...
さて 宴会の準備を始めるか！
Now, then! Let's get things ready for the party!
おっ？ おっ…
んっ？
I'm watching you.
なっ！ はあっ…
どうしたの？ オカリン
What's wrong, Okarin?
何でもない
Nothing.
これは…
What is this?
I think sweet curry is good.
カレーは甘口がいいかな？
それとも辛口？
Or maybe spicy?
What do you think?
どっちがいいと思う？
S-Sure... Spicy, I guess.
あっ ああ… 辛口でいいだろう
そっか～
鈴さんは バイト戦士だもんね
Oh, yeah! Suzu-san's a part-time warrior, right?
If she's a warrior, she'll want spicy.
戦士といったら
やっぱり 辛口だよね
え～っと 次は お肉 お肉！
Um... Next, we need the meat.
ほえ～ やっぱり 牛肉は高いよ
Beef is expensive...
ねえ オカリン
なんか 元気ないよ？
Hey, Okarin.
You don't look good.
Back there, you would've normally said...
さっきだって いつもなら
｢機関の妨害工作で
牛肉が とっても高い
"The Organization's sabotage has
increased the price of beef!
オペレーション･タイムセールは
まだか？｣
Has Operation Time Sale begun?"
とか 言ったりするのに…
ふん… そこは
タイムセールではなく 北欧神話だ
But you use Norse mythology there,
not "time sale."
俺だ 機関の妨害により
It's me.
The Organization's sabotage has
caused unexpected expenses
オペレーション･アウズンブラの
実行に 予想外の出費が生じた
in Operation Audhumbla.
作戦資金の増額を要請する
I'm requesting additional funds for the operation.
あっ… ああ 一番星！
The first star!
宵の明星か
Venus?
ねえ オカリン…
うん？
Hey, Okarin?
オカリンって小学生の頃
Remember in elementary school,
すごい熱 出して 寝込んだこと
あったよね
when you got really sick, with a high fever?
ああ…
Yes. The world was panicking
over the Y2K problem.
世間では2000年問題が
騒がれていた時期だったか
Mayushii was really scared you would die then.
あの時ね まゆしぃは
オカリンが
死んじゃうんじゃないかって
すごく 怖かったんだ
So I prayed to the sky.
だからね お空に祈ってたの
そしたらね
流れ星が ピュ～って １つ
And then, there was a falling star.
まゆしぃは流れ星に
I said to the falling star,
｢オカリン 死なないで｣って
３回 唱えたの
"Don't die, Okarin!" three times.
そしたら 次の日には
And the next day, you got better!
オカリンの熱が下がって
目を覚ましたんだ
だから まゆしぃは オカリンの
命の恩人なんだよ… へへへ…
And so I saved your life.
いいや 違うな
No, that's not true.
It was the choice of Steins Gate
あの状況で助かったのは
運命石の扉の選択だ
that I survived back then.
ええ～ そうなの？
Was it?
It was.
そうなのだ
そっか…
I see.
ねえ 熱を出して倒れた時
Hey, remember what you said,
オカリン
こんなこと言ったの 覚えてる？
when you got sick and collapsed?
｢急に 見ているものが
グニャグニャしてきて
"Everything I saw began to flow together,
立っていられなくて フラフラして
and suddenly, I shook and couldn't stand up."
体が ビクっとなった｣って
この前
フェリスちゃんのマンションでも
You looked just like that
オカリン
そんな感じだったんだよ？
in Feyris-chan's condominium.
熱を出して 倒れた時の
あの感覚…
That feeling I had when I got that fever
世界線を移動したときの感覚に
とても 似ている
was just like the feeling I get
when I move world lines.
ということは
Which means...
I attained my magic eye, Reading Steiner,
魔眼 運命探知は
at that moment?
まさに あの時
この身に宿ったということか…
ただいま～
おかえりなさい
We're back!
Welcome back.
うん？ 何か異臭がしないか？
You smell something weird?
I think it's the smell of Kurisu-san's apple pie.
多分 紅莉栖さんの作ってる
アップルパイの臭いだと…
What?
なに!? これがか？
This?
Want Mayushii to help, too?
まゆしぃも 手伝おうか？
Can you boil an egg?
じゃあ 卵をゆでててくれる？
Sure!
は～い！ え～っと…
Um... Can I use the microwave?
電話レンジ 使っていいかな？
ダッ ダメです！
生卵を入れたら 爆発しちゃいます
N-No!
If you put drop a raw egg in, it will explode!
I'll make the egg.
卵は僕が…
ええ～
So you chop up the mushrooms, Mayuri.
それじゃあ
まゆりは シイタケ刻んでおいて
Okay!
は～い
W-Wait!
待て！ アップルパイに
シイタケもゆで卵も 必要なかろう
You don't need mushrooms
or boiled eggs for apple pie!
It's for the salad, to go with it.
付け合わせのサラダに使うのよ
I don't think a boiled egg and mushroom salad
really goes with apple pie.
アップルパイに
シイタケとゆで卵のサラダを
付け合わせるのも
いかがなものか…
And you!
そこ！ 勝手に シイタケを…
Stop chopping up mushrooms over there!
ああ どいて どいて！
Move!
ふっ！ うぐぐ…
俺だ どうやら 邪神の封印を
解いてしまったらしい…
It's me.
It seems I've released the seals
that bound a dark god.
もし １時間以内に
連絡がなかったら
If I don't contact you within the hour,
両親に伝えてくれ
｢愛していた｣と…
tell my parents that I loved them.
Okabe-san, do you have a rice cooker?
岡部さん 炊飯器はありますか？
フェイリスたんは!?
Where's Feyris-tan?
フェイリスたんは いずこ？
橋田 あんた だまされてるわよ
Hashida, you've been deceived.
Feyris-san said she couldn't come.
フェイリスさんは
来られない って言ってたから
ちょっ… マジで？
おい オカリン！
Seriously?
Hey, Okarin!
Next time I get a chance, I'll take care of it.
次の機会があったら
話は つけておく
ふざけんなよ！ せっかく
タイムマシン オフ会だったのに…
Screw you!
I was really looking forward to my
time machine forum meeting.
タイムマシン オフ会？
Time machine forum?
僕が よく見に行く
ＳＦ関係のＢＢＳのオフ会
It's with a sci-fi message board I frequent a lot.
プロの作家も来る予定
だったのに…
A professional author was supposed to go, too!
This is an interestingly shaped mess kit.
これ 面白い形のはんごうですね
あっ 触るな！
そいつは はんごうじゃない…
Don't touch it.
That's not a mess kit.
It's Future Gadget #4, The Moad Snake.
未来ガジェット４号
｢モアッド･スネーク｣だ
A claymore mine?
クレイモア地雷…
に模して作られた
It's made to look like one.
超瞬間加湿器だ…
あっ これか！
It's a super-instant humidifier.
Oh, this?
えっ ああ… やっ やめろ！
S-Stop! Don't!
あっ！
うわあ！
あっ…
うわあ…
ああ…
ごめんなさい 岡部さん
I'm sorry, Okabe-san.
ふふっ…
過ぎたことは しかたがない
Don't worry about it.
Next time, don't touch it.
次からは うかつに触るな
Hey, couldn't we use this?
ねえ これ 使えるんじゃない？
掃除機… ですか？
A vacuum cleaner?
Nope!
違うよ 未来ガジェット３号
あれ… ２号だっけ？
It's Future Gadget #3.
Or #2?
#5!
５号だ
And its name is
その名も ｢また つまらぬものを
つなげてしまった ｂｙ 五右衛門｣
"Once Again I've Connected Something Useless
By Goemon."
掃除機の排気を
We made it so you can use a
vacuum cleaner's output to warm a dryer.
ドライヤーの温風に
利用できるようにしたものだお
Give it to me.
貸してみ？
Wait!
待て！ それを使うときは ほかの
電化製品の電源を 切らなければ…
When you use that, you need to turn off
any other appliances, or...
あっ…
ブレーカーが落ちる
...it'll trigger the breaker.
へえ…
Where's the flashlight?
懐中電灯 どこだっけ？
Is this it?
これですか？
違う るか氏 それ大根
No, Miss Ruka.
That's a daikon radish.
えっと ブレーカーは…
U-Um, where's the breaker?
If you walk around...
お～い 動き回ると…
ああっ！
だから…
I told you...
Ow...
あっ たったった…
ブレーカーは玄関だ
The breaker's in the front hall.
ううっ…
Are you okay?
大丈夫か？
フフフ フッ ハハッ…
何が おかしい？
What's so funny?
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい でも…
But...
The lab I worked at in America had some of
私のいるアメリカの研究所って
the best people from around the world.
世界中から優秀な人たちが
集まってるんだけど
But they all had really big heads,
みんな プライドが高くて
結構 殺伐としてるのよね
so it was a really hostile place.
Compared to them, your lab is really childish,
それに比べて
あんたのラボは
幼稚だけど 居心地がいい
but it's a fun place to be.
I-I'm not praising you, okay?
べっ… 別に
褒めてるわけじゃないからな！
I was just kinda thinking that...
ただ なんとなく
そう思っただけというか…
I guess maybe I simply wanted friends.
俺は
友達が欲しかっただけなのかもな
あっ！
I, um...
私は えっと…
I think of you as a companion.
仲間だと思ってるよ
You told me before, didn't you?
前に 言ってくれたでしょ？
That I was your dear companion.
私のこと 大切な仲間だって
That made me really happy, I guess.
あれ
結構 うれしかったっていうか…
You got a fever?
熱でもあるのか？
あっ… ねっ ねえよ！
N-No!
What? I'm trying to rethink my opinion of you...
なによ！ せっかく あんたのこと
見直してやってるのに…
Stupid Okabe!
この バカ岡部！
はっ！
あっ…
ふあ～ ああ…
鈴さん 遅いねえ…
Suzu-san's late.
I wonder if she met her dad.
お父さんに 会えたかな？
I bet they're finally spending time together.
今頃 水入らずの時間を
過ごしてるんじゃない？
どちらにしても ラボには来いと
言ったはずなのだが…
I told her to come to the lab, either way.
But it's late.
しかし この時間では もう遅い
作戦は中止だ
お前たちは もう帰れ
We're aborting the operation.
You guys, go on home.
うん？
あっ…
From: Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
Darn her!
ヤツめ！
はっ はっ はっ…
このまま 一人さみしく
この町を 離れるつもりなのか？
Does she plan to leave this city, by herself?
I, Hououin Kyouma, will not allow that!
そんなことは
この 鳳凰院 凶真が許さん！
くそっ！ いったい どこに…
Damn it!
Where did she go?
あっ！
That's right...
そうだ Ｄメールを使って
今日の昼間の俺に
If I send a D-mail, telling myself to follow her,
no matter what, this afternoon...
｢何があっても 鈴羽を尾行しろ｣と
But...
だが…
Is it right for me to use the D-mail
いいのか？
これ以上 Ｄメールを使っても
to change the past any more?
過去を改変してもいいのか？
You're a good person, you know that?
君って いいヤツだね
I feel a bit better now, somehow.
なんか
ちょっとだけ 楽になったかも
I am the great Mad Scientist, Hououin Kyouma!
俺は
狂気の マッドサイエンティスト
鳳凰院 凶真！
What have I to fear?
何を恐れることがあるというのだ
フ～ッハッハッハ…
フッハッハッハッハ…
Do not give in to your assistant's threats.
助手の脅迫に屈せず…
Follow Suzuha!
ううっ！ うう…
うっ… はっ！
はっ！
Yo.
う～っす！
おはよう バイト戦士
Good morning, part-time warrior.
Slacking off?
サボり中か？
Last night, we were all up really late.
昨日は
夜中まで 上で騒いでたからさ
I'm so tired.
すっごい 眠いんだよね…
Last night,
俺たちは 昨日の夜
お前が 父親に会えなかったので
we had a last supper for you,
実験台となってもらうための
最後の晩さんを開いた
so you could be our guinea pig.
そうだな？
Right?
But the experiment never happened.
実験は できなかったけどね
I don't know my dad's phone's address.
父さんの携帯のアドレスが
分かんなかったから…
I want to confirm something.
一つ 確認したいのだが
俺は いったい
どうやって お前を確保した？
How did I catch you?
君 お酒 飲んでた？
Were you drinking?
You're underage. You shouldn't do that.
未成年のくせに ダメなんだぞ～
Just answer me.
いいから 聞かせてくれ！
Well, I was heading back from the
time machine forum meeting...
え～っと… あたしが
タイムマシン オフ会から
帰ろうとしたら
Time machine forum?
タイムマシン オフ会？
That's where your dad was supposed to show up?
そこが 父親の現れるかもしれない
という場所だったのか？
うん あたしの父さんは
｢タイター｣って名乗ってるんだ
Yeah, my dad's calling himself Titor.
John Titor?!
ジョン･タイターか？
Not John... Barrel.
ジョンじゃなくて バレル
｢バレル･タイター｣
Barrel Titor.
I told you that yesterday.
それも 昨日 話したよね？
Didn't you take a video of it on your phone?
君 携帯ムービー
撮ってなかったっけ？
あ～あ 昨日は楽しかったな
I had fun last night...
It would've been more fun
without Makise Kurisu, though.
牧瀬 紅莉栖さえいなければ
もっと 楽しめたけどさ
Her apple pie was man-killingly horrible.
あいつのアップルパイ
殺人的なまずさだったし
But Urushibara Ruka's curry was great!
でも
漆原るかのカレーは 極上だった
Your lab's kinda nice, you know?
君たちのラボってさ なんかいいね
Everyone's friends, and you
always seem to have fun.
みんなが仲良くて
いつも楽しそうで
I've never felt so much like I
fit in somewhere, in my whole life.
あんな居心地のいい時間は
生まれて初めてだったよ
Then you're welcome anytime.
ならば 遠慮は要らん
いつでも 来ればいい
Come whenever you like.
You're a lab member now.
お前は もう ラボメンなのだ
Yeah.
うん もうちょっとだけ
I'll try and search for my father a little more!
頑張って 父さん 捜してみるよ！